CURRICULUM VITAE

ORKHAN R. ASGARZADE

Birth date:5 January 1991Mob: +972 58 793 7594Country/City: Israel, Bat YamMarital status:MarriedE-mail: oasg91@mail.ruZip/Postal code: 5930218

in

www.linkedin.com/in/asgarzade-orkhan

Summary

Internationally certified Drilling Data Analyst with offshore experience more than 5 years in the Deep-Water horizons on 11 various platforms of the Caspian Sea area, where successfully completed drilling challenging wells including ERD, Coring and sidetracks from beginning until completion operation. Seashore/Shipyard Construction Engineer experience with successful underwater project designs. Petroleum, Reservoir, Drilling Engineering, and Project Management (PMI) background. Proficient in data management, real-time monitoring SCADA/HMI, and formation-well evaluation, drilling data processing and interpretation, primary Well Control. Moreover strong background in Industrial Engineering (Mechanical, Chemical, Pipeline, Hydrology (Surface and Underground), Automation).

Education

BSc. Petroleum and Reservoir Engineer

2008 – 2012 Azerbaijan State University of Oil and Industry/Azerbaijan State Oil Academy (Grade A)

MSc. Offshore Drilling Engineering

2013 – 2015 Azerbaijan State University of Oil and Industry/Azerbaijan State Oil Academy (Honor)

Postmaster Project Management, PMP/PMI

2016 Technion – Israel Institute of Technology (400 academic hours)

Work Experience

2019/3 – 2020/9 Chemo Aharon Ltd., Israel – Quality/Quantity Assurance Engineer

Acting as a catalyst for change and improvement in performance and quality. Assisted project Manager to perform recording, analyzing, and distributing statistical information, cost management through SIEMENS data management system-ICMMS. Proven experience to manage field work and negotiating with client.

SCHLUMBERGER, Azerbaijan branch

2017/4 – 2019/3 Drilling Data Analyst/Engineer: Provided services on 11 various offshore platforms controlling incoming

wellbore data and collaborating with the client and 3rd parties' representatives in case of any discrepancies.

Achieved 5 years extension of contract with BP.

2014/1 – 2016/3 Mud Logging Analyst: Provided services on 11 various offshore platforms assisting Data Analyst to monitor the

well status and cooperated with WSG to analyze and evaluate drilled formation in Laboratory and report.

2012/6-9 <u>Eni S.p.A, Azerbaijan branch</u> – Project Construction Engineer

Lead the construction by following the fabrication of project equipment. Design in AutoCAD.

2011/9 - 2012/6 Azerbaijan State University of Oil and Industry - Petroleum and Reservoir Engineering Department

Built reservoir model through software RMS, Kappa, and Surfer. Research on the innovative technology of

petroleum and reservoir industry, especially nanotechnology application for EOR.

Publication Technology of Petroleum Production

2012 Published by Azerbaijan State University of Oil and Industry and Oil and Gas Research Center

2012/10 – 2013 Military Service

Servicing as a Radio communicator/Chief radio communicator in the Azerbaijan Army

Offshore Trainings:

Formation Evaluation (Mud Logging/Interpretation) Analyst, Data (Acquisition System) Engineer/Analyst, SCADA/HMI FUET, BOSIET, MSDS, COSHH, S-Cape

Qualifications and Certificates

Society of Petroleum Engineers (SPE) presenter: Oil and Gas Wells Drilling, Directional Drilling, (ERD–2018)

Certificate of 2011-2012 Work Readiness Project of **Junior Achievement** Azerbaijan (2012)

American Association of Petroleum Geologists (AAPG) presenter: Nanotechnology application to Petroleum Production (2012)

Academic Conference Certificate - thesis: Nanotechnology application to petroleum production (2011-2012)

Caspian Engineers Society – Certificate of offshore operation process and technology course (2010)

Other: Data privacy & protection, Well integrity, Emergency Response Drill, H2S, Fire Safety, Pressure, Radiation Level 1, OBM & SBM safe handling. Schlumberger QHSE, SIPP, Maersk Explorer's HSE, SHELL Think Safety etc.

Language kills

English: proficient; Russian: proficient; Turkish: proficient; Hebrew: intermediate.

Computer skills

- RMS Geological Modelling, Well Planning (ROXAR AS. and Equinor / (Stat Oil ASA.)); Nano Educator (MacOS system).
- Auto CAD/SolidWorks/Navisworks, MS Office, Windows, MacOS, Linux.
- Gantt, MS Project (Basic), ICMMS (SIEMENS system)

Orkhan R. Asgarzade 1